A beautiful secluded Island.... Five good
friends... And a killer out for revenge.
Fear Island is a horror, thriller, mystery film directed by Michael Storey.
Five students on spring break meet at a secluded
island cabin for a weekend getaway.
Stranded on the island they become the prey of a mysterious killer who
seems bent on revenge for something the friends have done.
Mark, played by Aaron Ashmore.
Jenna, played by Haylie Duff.
Megan, played by Lucy Hale.
Tyler, played by Kyle Schmid.
Dr. Jamie Chalice, played by Anne Marie DeLuise.
Kyle Campbell, played by Jacob Blair.
Fear Island is a 2009 Canadian mystery-thriller film directed by Michael Storey
and starring Aaron Ashmore, Haylie Duff, Lucy Hale and Kyle Schmid.
The film follows five student friends partying on a remote island, when they
find a dead body and encounter a killer who wants them all dead.
Fear Island was released direct-to-video on September 8, 2009, in
Canada and on June 28, 2010, in the United States.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.